Lã Mai Win

Front-End Developer

imlinkedin.2108win

github.com/2108win



I am a Front-end Developer with over 1 year of experience developing UI/UX for web applications. Experience developing responsive and accessible web applications.

Seeking to enhance my skills as a Front-End Developer in a collaborative environment, with a short-term goal of mastering advanced JavaScript frameworks, and a long-term goal of leading projects that deliver exceptional user experiences.

Lã Mai Win

Front-End Developer

@<u>win_lax</u> linkedin.2108win @<u>winlax2108@gmail.com</u> & (+84) 0971292838

INFO

August 21, 2001

O HCMC, Vietnam

SKILLS

Core Technology

JavaScript(ES6+), TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3/SASS/SCSS.

UI Frameworks and JS Libraries

React.js, Next.js, Framer Motion, GSAP, Styled Components, TailwindCSS.

Other Tools

Sanity, Pug, Reactform-hook, Zustand, Zod, Tanstack/reacttable, Angular, Vercel, Figma, Adobe XD.

LANGUAGE

- Vietnamese (Native)
- English (Basic)
- Japanese (Q3, ~N3)

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree of University of Information Technology VNU-HCM 2024

- Major: Information Technology (Japanese-oriented)
- **GPA:** 7.5

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer @ LoaTaiXuong

Feb 2024 - Present

Technology: React.js (useEffect, useState, useRef), Next.js, TypeScript, Zustand, Zod, React-form-hook, Tanstack/react-table, TailwindCSS (Shadcn/ui), RESTful API.

- 1. Homepage *loataixuong.com*
- Top 3 SEO ranking for "Loa tại xưởng" using Next.js for speed and optimization.
- User-friendly e-commerce platform for seamless customer experience.
- 2. Admin panel page <u>dsl-admin.vercel.app</u>
- CRUD operations (Create, Read, Update, Delete) with RESTful API.
- Role-based access control.
- · Routing and form handling.
- Mobile-friendly UI design.

Front-End Developer Intern @ VDTC - ePass

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Technology: Angular, TypeScript, SCSS.

- Learn and improve coding skills with the framework Angular.
- Fixed interface errors, added new features.
- Updated login and forgot password UI at <u>customer.epass-vdtc.com.vn</u>.
- Developed internal website (UI/UX, layout, functions) to collect ideas and reduce work process by 50%.
- Received a perfect 10/10 evaluation for internship.

PROJECTS

Front-End Developer @ WinLax-Portfolio

Jun 2024 - Present

Technology: Next.js, TailwindCSS (Shadcn/ui), Animation (GSAP, Framer-Motion), Sanity.

- My page <u>winlax-portfolio.vercel.app</u>.
- The user interface is very nice and great animation.